&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：有一件事我认为在打字稿中被低估了，这是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One thing that I think is undervalued within TypeScript this is
实际上我更多的虫子是从哪里来的。
actually where many more of my bugs have come from.
除了能够静态输入信息之外
It's that in addition to being able to a static typing information about
变量赋值，它还可以告诉我们某些操作将是无效的。
variable assignments, it can also tell us that certain operations would be invalid.
在这个特殊的例子中，它说你不能从一个数字中减去一个字符串。
In this particular case, it's saying you can't subtract a string from a number.
因为那个特殊的偏好是说不允许强迫，并且
Because that particular preference is saying don't allow that coercion, and
在这个特殊的情况下，这对我来说是一个非常有用的帮助。
in this particular case, that would be a really useful help for me.
我真的很想
I would really like for
一个Linter告诉我，不要试图从一个数字中减去一个字符串。
a linter to tell me, don't try to subtract a string from a number.
我真正想要的是一件让我拥有它的短裤，但是
What I'd really like is a linter that let me have that, but
不让我对我所有的静态类型作业有所有的抱怨。
not let me have all the complaints about all my static type assignments.
那是我的偏好。
That would be my preference.
但我认为，这是他们所做的事情中被低估的一部分。
But this is, I think, an undervalued part of what they do.
他们实际上允许我们检查操作
Is that they are actually allowing us to check the operations that
我们正在做我们大部分业务逻辑所在的地方，并且
we're doing where most of our business logic is, and
确保这些操作有效。
making sure that those operations are valid.
如果TypeScript有一些机制，您可以允许这样做，那就太好了
It would be nice if TypeScript would have some mechanism by which you could allow
更多的胁迫会发生。
some more coercion to occur.
因为有很多地方，正如我已经提出的那样，
Because there are plenty of places, as I've already made the case,
在那里，我希望能够进行强制和其他地方，我希望避免它。
where I'd like to be able to do coercion and other Places I'd like to avoid it.
在我看来，在我的研究中，打字稿是一种要么全部要么什么都没有。
It appears to me in my research that Typescript is kind of all or nothing.
你要么选择加入，要么不选择。
You opt into it or you don't opt into it.
我更喜欢有更多的细微差别和配置。
I'd prefer there to be more nuance and configuration.